Okay, yeah, it's kind of hard to expose somebody when the person's trying to you know
He won't leave me the video, right? So that's that's something I think he like
He thinks like I'm trying to get credit for exposing him or something. No, I mean anybody looks like I would have given full credit and everything but
If you want to be petty like that, I can just restart and we can, you know, it'll be on
my Discord.
Or the video is on my old Discord, I'll put it on my new one too though.
And we can have that on there.
So I don't know if my Discord is going to look like my Discord thing for you guys.
My new Discord is this one.
And I didn't, I mean, I would have gotten back to that video sooner, but like I said,
I lost access to that discord.
I mean, I had watched like probably like five minutes
of that video, just probably should have been bad enough.
But again, I was trying to give the benefit of the doubt,
but, you know, so let me post my discord.
Yeah, he's a big pussy.
It's my video.
Well, I was gonna, that would have helped.
I mean, I'm looking, maybe it would have helped this case,
but, you know, just go ahead.
We can just, I'll just have a...
I'll put him a brand and it says be the last where I'm uncangled, right?
He wants to be like that.
He's not perfect either.
And then trip and sip, oh, oh, is that gonna help you, champ?
Listen, I'm already facing the consequences.
I know I'm facing the consequences and I know.
And I can say I made a mistake and I can say I'm sorry.
What else can I do, right?
But also, he also repeated lies about me,
animal, abuser, blah, blah, blah.
Or do you guys know everything?
Do you guys know about, like, I could not have
a conversation with Crystal about these things
or him or anything like that,
because I would just be attacked.
You know, I could have had a conversation.
They wouldn't.
They just want to attack me about me, right?
So, can you see what?
I'd be upset with him, right?
And the only reason he wouldn't let me play in that
is because he wants some kind of
Credit for being some kind of like hero or something like that and he's and he's thinking that
Old dim is light because you know
He's not allowed on YouTube or he is I guess but not really he was banned for three years or whatever, but
Whatever
So
Okay
Yeah, we know Britt. We know he's not perfect, right? We know he's not perfect, too
I mean, is anybody perfect?
That's the whole thing.
It's like, why, but then when I,
when someone's trying to make things right,
why would you then keep attacking them, right?
I don't understand it.
I'm trying to be like, oh, finally,
like, you know, someone's listening to my,
but no, he's gonna say, I'm gonna strike you.
That's my video.
I own that.
It's my, it's unlisted.
I mean, maybe if it was like,
I mean, I wish I could, you know,
somebody I could respect would have shared it, you know?
instead of like gamble, gamble Tony, you know.
And immediately I was being called names
and so I'll get defensive and I'll double down.
You know, it's like, listen, hate bonding is real.
All these kinds of things are real.
It's like, am I perfect?
No, did I, if I participated in these things?
Yes, and so, you know, but it's a pretty normal behavior.
Why am I still repeating BS, Brandon Spoon fed me?
No, I mean, it's like he spoon fit. He didn't spoon feed me anything
But so much for Alex being best to get a journalist. Okay. Well, you know, um, no, she's mad at me
She's mad at me. She says that I it's my fault
and
you know, I
Apologize I broke away from him earlier than she did. Yeah, I got the link for you then but um, and then but then
It was my fault, you know
Yeah, there are life. I guess you did lie about gamble, but I mean see what I mean, I need to get
I'm not a police officer. I'm not I'm not a public
defendant. I'm not a
Defense attorney. I'm not a lawyer. I'm just a person. It's like most of you people like we're just people watching some of this stuff
So, you know, listen, you don't need to attack each other. Let's welcome to the show Ion X
It's like a gamble was telling the truth and I needed to see the proof of that idiot's been telling me that gamble was sending me a virus because he wouldn't play
for some reason and
Somebody else sent it to me this morning. I'm done with that asshole. All he does is talk about gamble gamble didn't hurt kids
Years ago, I think some young guy was on his a panel with a bunch of streamers and there was not nothing weird going on
And his name was Daniel and it was nothing. It was years ago. I think he would gamble. He was it was years ago
But it wasn't head or anything and so he's not he called out a pedal and that's Brandon
He's been threatening my life and blown me up because I know the truth
He's telling me gamble sent you virus you stupid bitch, you know, fuck you asshole
You don't know who you're fucking with Brandon and you just try to call my text down number that I've been recording you on
You're a piece of shit
And I'm gonna play all those recordings. You're obsessed with gamble that Chris rock was not in communication with you
You you're obsessed with gamble and you need to shut up and I told you that and then you caught me a bitch
And I'm gonna die you're gonna kill my pets all this shit. You're insane and I don't want anything to do with you
I mean, and he's making all these alts to get in to fuck with people. I'm done. He's crazy
yep
And and Gamble I wish he'd let you use those videos because people need to see it
Most people don't haven't seen that shit on him and he's over there calling
Gamble a petto everybody else is a petto about him and I haven't seen those other videos
I was looking at that because I'd like to share him too. Yeah, I was actually trying to play this play this video
Yeah, because I told you this guy is an asshole Brandon and look at the trouble he got you in
Me because a lot of people blocked me because of him even Barry the K all of them because they said hey
She's um, you know talking to this psycho because Alex said he was a good guy
And I don't know I knew there was something not right about him
Because when I finally saw that video of him going at that dog
He was crazy and that's exactly who I see now. You've seen him act like that on your panels
He just turns on you and goes crazy
He came up as like a soft-spoken quiet kind of polite right I met him and it's like you know
And, you know, and I, I have also been, you know, bullied or, you know, and there's a lot of accusations and so I was just kind of slow, very slow.
But then it's like, then I had all these people that I considered like, you know, not my friends trying to tell me what to do about it.
Yeah, yeah.
So maybe, and then maybe it turned into something else, but hey, I'm turning on subscriber only mode.
I'm glad you're showing the truth because he lied about Gamble being banned from YouTube. That's not true.
He's in a relationship or something. I didn't know he lied to me about everything gamble is able to get on
He's not afraid to get on
he's just brandon is a piece of shit liar and he just lies and then we have the the truth you know he
just makes up shit alex did not donate a thousand dollars to him and then later he said it was four
thousand when he told me on the phone nobody gives me money i said well i thought you just said that
alex gave you a lot of money oh she just wants me to impregnate her and that's why she came to
albuquerque i'm going to show all of that though i'm sick of him
He needs to leave me alone. He's still trying to call my text outnumbered. I've been recording him on that.
Yeah. Let me see. Messages. Let me see. Okay, yeah. Well, yeah. I mean, now we can...
You know take a breath and like you know now. I mean it's been it's been a big whirlwind of stuff happening, right?
And it's been a lot with him. Yeah, and I would have I would have had that video to watch earlier
But like I said shortly after that video was sent to me. I lost my my discord
I wasn't able to log into that because I did try to I wanted to play that video a few times for him to like it to get like
you know his
His take on it, but yeah
Can you give him credit for that because I don't think he has those videos up because most of your chat are shocked at what you showed him
It's like oh my god, that's him. That's the way I felt because I felt for the
of the fake nice Brandon when Alex told us to, you know, you know, support him, and then
he goes crazy, mostly gamble, gamble, gamble, gamble, he put a sent you a virus bitch, gamble
and I'm gonna kill you, go die, I have those texts, I had almost sent him to Crystal a
few weeks ago, and then he apologized and he goes nuts.
And I blocked him and he's gonna show my whole picture from 2016 when you've seen me.
and I've been FaceTime with people.
I mean, he's insane and look at him,
but these videos are shocking
because I didn't see these other videos.
The only one that I'd seen before
was him hitting on a 13-year-old girl.
I think you showed part of that.
Maybe that was by Gamble,
but that was the only thing I had seen.
Yeah, yes, okay.
So, I mean, I'm trying to figure out the subscriber
only mode that there is like some kind of...
Stuff going on. It is kind of difficult to figure out. Yeah, I hope yeah, I hope gamble let's you keep those videos
Because you know what gamble has that video on listed? He doesn't want people to see it unless he
Oh, yeah, so let him show it again. He could be the hero
I mean, but no, he's not gonna people like me like what do you do the private? Oh, I think yeah
But I mean people need to see the people in your chat
We're shocked cuz a lot of people don't know about Brandon and that needs to be out because he's trying to put all this shit out on
Gamble is mostly fake falling out like I he's been banned from the show probably for like at least three weeks
I don't understand why people are saying this is brand new
I mean people you you guys are very brand new too, but he's been he's been banned from the show for quite a while
Really? Yeah, and then he'll make all these crazy alts to join in any way. I mean he does that with the
Text I don't know. He's just the guy is an hinge and he's insane and that kick video. I hope I hope you can play that
That was from kick. Yeah, he said striking. He said striking and then I was like, well, yeah
I know I don't know but then that's what Brandon wants. He wants them struck down. Yeah, okay. Well, I mean
Okay, well, I know
We all know about him. No, we didn't the thing. No, I didn't I didn't I only saw one video that I shared a long time ago
And I left it alone because Alex was ignored it and you know, then she told us he's good and give him a chance
so
I don't know and then I thought maybe she's right because I only saw that one video
But the one non-kick you got you can play that one now the one that I sent you
Trying to I was trying to play the video
I was editing a second then you came into that name
Which makes you think that you were him and then it's like you're like that's my no
I'm I'm grateful to 2026. That's me. Oh, no, I don't have any Alton count. That's I come in as myself
Guys and please leave that poor person from Laguna Niguel alone. I don't know what this was by this person
Yeah, but at least that one you can show because I think I recognize that name
That person used to be on YouTube and it's their video and it's on kick
So play that one because I'm gonna post it and who are you who are you then then I'm gonna put your real name in the
Because you did say don't play it and I mean if you're gonna strike me, right?
Who's gonna strike you know
Person Brandon loves kids in the in the chat like yeah, I don't know who it is
I don't know crystal posted that account and and they said that was probably Ganville
I don't know who that account is but
The kick video is it's from kick you can play that one
Everybody needs to see that one look at how he went at the dog
And I think that was twice that he went there and that guy that's with him
That's who get who he says it was Gamble's friend that sent him to Albuquerque that didn't make sense because it looks like it's his friend.
The same guy he took to a fake Clovis to harass our clumsy because if you look at it because when we were talking to him, he was going to go live.
And then he said, hang on, my friend just came over here,
we're going to Clovis right now, we're on the way there.
And then 20 minutes, he's back and ready.
And I lived in Albuquerque.
We had a football championship game
against Clovis High School, and that's a four hour trip.
I remember my mom took us there.
And I didn't say anything to him that the other day
when I was talking to him, he mentioned Clovis.
And I said, how far is it from Albuquerque?
Because I was in high school when I was there and he said four hours and I thought and I looked at the text and I thought wait a minute
You were gone 20 minutes and that wasn't even
Clovis he was in his own neighborhood with that same guy that he says was Gamble's friend that he sent him to him the
album nothing makes sense
But yeah, he was in his own neighborhood pretending. He's over there in Clovis
harassing clumsy saying, oh, he came out the door and he looked scared and he ran back in.
Bitch you weren't in Clovis. You were in Albuquerque
Saying I told you so but I'm just saying
You did say the videos before psyche you saw them before
They were they were given to them the channel was given to them
Yeah, I only saw one video with the girl and that was it and then
Uh, yeah, I didn't know.
I'm showing them, like, because you're my other brand, and you saw...
What's going on again? Fuck outta here, bitch! They're out!
He he was threatening psyche with fake accounts. Yeah, I mean, it's like yes, I understand
I mean I'm gonna say I mean geez
I can I say it again, but listen, I didn't see those videos you just showed the only one I thought was a 13-year-old
Look, yeah, when I got that so I never watch a little thing. I didn't look for it. Yeah
Yeah in a video. He just wants to be a little bitch
Trippin sit your bitchy whiny voice is too much for me to handle this morning. Okay, I'm reducing important where I'm not
Whatever videos you have and I hope Gamble's okay with it. I'll give him credit. I'll show them. I mean, I don't care
Yeah, I didn't see all that. I've never known. I knew I heard he was a bad person. I shared the video
that KK
Posted and somebody struck it down, but it was of him hitting on that 13-year-old girl
Where she's drinking and she's in eighth grade. That was the only one I had and I don't know why Alex didn't pay attention to that
I mean, it's obvious, you know that he's sick, right? I mean it's like well
It's like yeah, there were mistakes made and that's like of course when we're
You're back into a corner like I was with with like a with like a lot of people right and then yeah
I don't know. It's like things happen, but it's like I wasn't like oh, this just happened
You know, I like I maybe it's like a late to be doing this expose. I was trying to do it when he was there
But it's like yeah, I would have known before I would have showed all that because I did share that one from KK
Yeah, well, I just found I was just able to get it again
I have been asking for it for like a couple weeks
But me too and they know send it till somebody else sent it to me because I asked crystal and she refused to even play it
For me to record it because I called them out on it
And he knew i couldn't get the video because he was watching crystals live because he was going off on me for being there he's just he stalks everybody it's like do life.
He's always in our gaming and talking to his bots.
You're both looking fake here, psyche and techie to say okay. Well thing that is no
It's not a thing that is you're the one that's always kissing ass and flip-flopping, you know
That's sad
No, nobody's blaming Alice remember the video of Ganvel's evil with Brandon with the with the Aaron Carter recovery with him and the
Angel wings and stuff like that and the other judges. Yeah, just keep posting that Laguna Miguel address. Please keep doing that
Yeah, then it's only a little bitch right now. It's like you're being told. Yeah, he's weird. Yeah, he flip flopped a lot
Yeah, he's a flip flopper. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Keep posting my mom's address on Los Osos driving
Go ahead. You're all at fault. Okay, but you know what? We're taking responsibility. Like, you know, are we both saying we made a mistake?
I mean, it's like huge mistake and and Brandon. I know you're watching. I'm done with you
I did make a police report because your information has been out there. So stop calling my text now
You know, I've been recording you on that. I do record on the text now number. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I have the ACR recording it automatically not on my regular phone, but it's on the text now
Yeah, oh, no this is well thing that is come on come on that now you're being you're being like
Why do you think it's a good thing that is antropons that have these voices?
That's what it's done like to me it sounds like some kind of like farm animal. Okay, what's my zodiac sign?
Yeah. Okay. I don't hear a bunch of like, you know, like, like, like, bleeding sheep in the chat.
We told you so. Yeah.
Okay. We don't... Listen.
I didn't know anything about him. I just only saw that video that I shared from KK.
Right.
And nobody said anything. And then when Alex said that he's a good guy, support him.
I fell for that shit and then I saw the crazy him when he started threatening me for being
In the chat and gamble was there said fuck you bitch. He's he's doing this to you and sending this
You know crazy. It's like I can go where I want and stop stalking everybody
Yeah, what you're saying?
Yeah, so guys, oh, you know, first of all, you know, the one thing that is true is like, you know
sometimes
We can change our minds, you know, like there are people that change our minds over every like little thing, but this is not that right?
This is not this is like
It's not even going back and forth. This is different. Yeah, it's different. I mean this guy is an actual pedo
okay, right
yeah, and
Crazy he's on his with the threats and all it's like that's the person I see in those videos him going nuts because that's him
because
because also
We were nothing but kind to this person and then the real side when the someone that's kind to somebody for no reason
we'll turn on them like a
Abuse dog or something like that, you know
I like that that has like some kind of like PTSD and just has to attack everybody. So yeah, you think for ourselves. That's why
Yeah, it's maybe took so long to get to this place. Right? We're not blaming Alex. I don't understand why you say you're blaming
Nobody's blaming Alex. She didn't know like me. She probably didn't see all the videos that she remember. It's nobody's fault
It's it's never told her. Oh, let's let's do a redemption arc for him and stuff like that
And you know, it was it was it all was very fast, right? I know gamble or look at this
Look, I love all the people say. Oh, you were warned like it's like yes, okay
We don't understand that you know
And yeah, gamble did try try to warn and I wasn't believing that because I thought no
He's he's not a petal, but now I saw the other videos it's other people sent me
And it's like yeah, and it's like and then too with that, you know again
We're going to semantics here, but it's like, you know, there's difference between
Not even legally or whatever, but okay, there's chicken cakes. How many people told you though there? Yeah, but you know
But chicken cakes 99% of these were ops of mine
I think I lost maybe 1% of people I actually cared about because of this not I mean, that's that's not even worth it right now
Yeah, like Barry and I was cool with Kate all these other people and they were mad at me
You know and a couple of them blocked me because I was giving him a chance thinking maybe they're wrong about him
Because I didn't see the other videos only the one with the 13 year old
And he almost sounded normal at first,
but then his true self came out where he's making threats.
I'm gonna kill you.
Go kill yourself, something about my pets.
He's just completely unhinged and crazy
and I'm done with it.
I'm not gonna give him any chances anymore.
He's insane and he's stalking me now,
making weird accounts.
So the thing is, what's the reason for changing your mind?
Well, he's been banned for several weeks from my show, right?
Yeah, he banned him a couple of weeks ago.
It was when he started to attack me for no reason, and then...
other fallouts happen and I'm and I all of a sudden, you know, I it's almost like I
Became or he tried to like try to switch places with me
We're now is like I'm being called the things like but he was calling he's like thinking that he you know
He's just really relevant. That's just that there are many people telling you but yeah many so a lot of people can say things
Right, it needs me somebody that you trust and the people first and I trusted
You know I trusted
You know my best friend at the time
You know and I guess you know, so we made a mistake, but you know, whatever
But the thing is did you see what he did to hurt a lion and saying she gave him a thousand dollar?
Don't know and then he's telling us on your panel. It was four thousand dollars when he told me later
Nobody gives me money and he's still going off about a hundred dollars. He claims I gave you
I didn't give you a hundred dollars and he said you said it on your live. No remember
I didn't want him on panel right
And you get one of them on panel and then he said I'll pay a hundred dollars. I said I'll match that remember that was that
And he left and there was no
There was no money exchanged. Yeah
So how much to ban? Well, he's it's not money because he's he's banned permanently. So
I don't have poop in my lip, you know, and he's still going on about the hundred dollars like when I just blocked him
Um, um, yeah black them this morning. You gave him a hundred dollars
I didn't give anybody $100 and why is it any of your business? Are you desperate? I mean, go make your own money.
But what is what he was wanting me to give him a hundred dollars fuck here?
I want to see where everyone has it where we were we've we said and watch all this evidence
There's because maybe the evidence was out there
Maybe it was we were directed towards us, but like I said, I did not have my access to my discourse shortly after that
Was sent we're not gonna be friends again. I don't know there's clumsy
I mean it's like see there's all people saying what will happen. Well, how do they know are they?
But clumsy you have some kind of like, you know, it's a Blue Heria powers or something like that
three more days, three hours, 26 minutes.
Well, that's how much longer maybe you have my chat.
Watch out guys, because it's like,
if you're gonna be sitting here like,
still like, you know,
because what else can I do besides this?
I mean, it's like, so, I mean, it's like, if I was to-
Just let the other people see the truth
and aren't done like we were by,
because we saw the signs, I just, I don't know.
And it's hard, it's hard, right?
So, oh, look at this, I'm like, okay, so clumsy.
Yeah, well, whatever, clumsy.
And clumsy, you had him on your show, am I correct?
Didn't, I actually, did clumsy have-
I don't think he ever had him on his show.
I think he was aware of him.
He was boxing his kid again.
It's like, who does he think he is?
You know, oh, well, he's in his 20s, bitch.
That's what he said on the phone.
I don't care, you're still showing somebody's kid.
Right.
Why is Q coming or G coming after him or what is?
No, I don't know he needs to be gone with the police. I mean he's just in hinge
he's making threats and and
Again, I mean clumsy posted an old picture from 2016
You've seen me and I posted what my last face time will not last a face time with somebody
That they shared it and I posted it. That's me now. I'm not bad at all. I'm thin and you saw me
Right. I know. I know. I mean, it's like that. Yeah, it's just he wants his war between everybody
I think I don't know what happened is he's just a piece of shit Brandon go away. Yeah. Yeah, we can make that any more clear
Yeah, yeah, I don't want shit to do with him, but watch him
He's gonna make a stupid shit on us and everything because he's crazy. He has no life
He's always in there gaming and talking to himself and has all these bots repeating the same thing that he says
Just like that fake
Message from Alex saying I'm so drunk right now, but you deserve this
$1,000 no because that's that's not her cash app name either because a couple years ago
She did a really cool video and I cashed after $25. I did because I liked it and she didn't ask or anything
That was that so I know her cash app name and it wasn't what he posted
Yeah
and everybody like to then say oh well he was paying psyche a lot of money for this and everything
yeah he says i'm paying you too that i gave you a hundred dollars no i can show my cash up no i hadn't
He sent me a grand total of $10 and so I mean, yeah, I know he tells me I got a thousand
I got this and then then you know when I last talked to him
Yeah, I didn't make any money and it was like well didn't you say that Alex sent you $1,000 and then you said it was
$4,000 what what's the what account that I bang gambled for telling the truth?
What was that? What was that? What was that? Who are you big dog Elizabeth that said I had it in my lip
Well, I don't see any band again. What's it? I peep my peepees bro, bro
Tomato mafia, which one are you because everyone was like saying I told you so I told you so I'll ban this one too
I don't care gambles cake. You're a dick too. You call me cat abuser before I even knew me
And so what's your evidence for that? So you were accusing me and saying things out of out of my name, right?
Because people said that to you, right?
Your only account, okay. Oh Gamble was kicked. Yeah, you should let him on I'm
But he's talking to us right now, so he's obviously not oh, okay
Yeah, he was telling the truth and here I was going at him calling him a liar and shit
And he's not a pedo. He wouldn't when has he done anything like that him and Shane Coyle exposed pedos
I didn't ban that. I didn't ban that account. I don't know who banned it. Let me see
I can go look in my chat. Oh, he was making some gamble alts too
And it was like that's not gamble just using his picture using some weird names. I don't think that's what he does
It was gamble. I
Don't see
No, I don't see he's obsessed with gamble like what is is he in love with him? I mean what the hell?
Oh, he's gone now because of me and I said no, he isn't I just saw him in a chat
Yeah, you know, it's like he's crazy and he lies about everything
Yeah, I don't see it was gamble hidden at all. I mean I didn't see that but I can go look in my band list
But let me see it. I don't see it at all. I hid Rob. I hid you six. I
Don't see it was game one. Is that it? No, nope
I mean, isn't it true though that everybody said that his own family didn't want him anymore
And he was raised by an uncle or aunt or something because he's crazy
Yeah, I didn't ban no, I know we don't gamble account was banned that it was gamble account was not banned. So yeah good
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I don't know what he's talking about people need to see that gamble
Please let him share it. I thought I thought it was gamble
I mean Brandon threatening you with striking you because he wants all that shit down
Yeah, yeah, he wants me to take down everything on him, too. You can join one second
I'm gonna put a link up again for you guys and here you go
But yeah, he was telling the truth and I the I should apologize to him and not
To him to it. It's like it's like if I say I'm sorry and then it's like I then it's like it's not not accepted
It's like instead of just like yeah, I know I understand but it's like but you've been yelling at me this whole time
You know, it's like so maybe like, you know, if you're finally vindicated you just like, you know, take it like I'm taking like my
No, he was a gamble was telling the truth
He did I get the video I get a crystal wouldn't send it to me. So then I thought okay
Well, then it's fake then you want don't want to send it
But he Brandon was watching the whole time and then he had a lot to say and I said yeah
Well, they didn't send it so don't worry about it cuz it's a lie. It's gambling and then I don't know. He's he's insane
I don't want shit to do with him. He's been blocked everywhere
And I see on my block list that he's still trying to call that text down number.
And guys, you have to understand, I do have ops, you know, I do have people that are opposed to me that are, and they are just jumping on any kind of thing to say anything, right?
Okay, so I guess Gamble's coming out.
Oh, yeah, that happens. That's gonna happen. It's gonna be other people.
Hello?
Hey, what's up nigger nigger that's him see that's not gamble it the gamble has one account and it's what you see
Yeah, yeah, you saw him and he has that image. Yeah, any other gamble is him. Yeah
Yeah, so that wasn't gamble in your chat. That's probably brand in the whole time
I didn't see your chat because I'm on my phone right now
Absolutely shocking. So yeah, the gamble wouldn't say he's gonna strike you. I don't think so was that that?
You know that account
No, gamble only uses his one account and it says it's called it was gamble and it's him like a Superman and a pink background
That's him 2020. Hey, hey, you unhide is you just timeout for 10 seconds Wow, you know, I hope gamble sees this
Yeah, and you know, I'm gonna use the videos that you have because I can
And no, I don't think Gamble, so that wasn't Gamble,
be careful, you've seen what Gamble looks like,
his account, he doesn't have any other account.
Yeah, okay, well, I'll change the title of my stream.
Yeah, just leave it the way it was before,
but yeah, Gamble, it wouldn't be going at you like that.
That's him making all these alts.
You can report that every alt that he has,
it takes time because somebody was doing that last year.
and she lost her, she couldn't get on YouTube anymore.
Yeah, I've been here multiple times.
Well, I've seen you once or twice in the chat, Gamble.
And I was actually receptive to talking to you too,
but when you just called me animal abuser and cat abuser.
Yeah, that's Brandon, that's not Gamble.
No, but that was no as I was gamble on crystal show. Oh, yeah on her show. Oh, yeah, okay
Yeah, so he did and that also like, you know, maybe we got off on the wrong foot, right?
But it's like it's certainly not the best but to to be accusing me of crimes, you know, especially
And I know somebody a close member of my family that went to Albuquerque to hurt somebody because of a bad blood from a long time ago
He's dangerous though and we're close
He's gonna he's gonna bring me some weed later. He gets really good weed
Isn't modded, but let me let me see what's going on with the robots. I got to see
Okay, I'm selling something on road mods. Let me see if I someone's being few who's being hit at noisy
Message is leaded by okay, if it was me with some troll or somebody that was talking shit or whatever
Bad Boy Breeze, are you?
Oh, Bad Boy Breeze shouldn't be banned.
Yeah, he was calling him gay and everything,
just rude when Bad Boy Breeze didn't do anything.
I didn't the gamble account.
So is that a fake one?
Is that a fake Bad Boy Breeze?
Hold on.
And here's a.
Bad Boy Breeze uses one account.
Extendo.
Like, hi.
How are you doing today?
I'm okay.
It's like a little, you know,
it's an interesting day.
I woke up to like,
Hey, baby, come here.
Yeah, you did a great video this morning, INX, like, you know, going through his voice or his text messages to you.
Yeah.
And I was about, I was uploading the video from kick that Gamble sent me about him attacking the dog and it wasn't once, it was twice.
and wait so okay wait hold on very interesting can you guys explain to me
what's going on a little bit so I can be like a couple months ago like Brandon
Hugh like started showing up in the chat and then kind of causing it up roar
because people are like oh no you know he's a he's a PDF like this and that and
and I got like some videos of my discord and but then also my discord
He was also posting a lot of stuff,
but there's this court,
so there's a lot of stuff being posted.
So I didn't go through everything,
and then I lost access to it.
In the meantime, Alexandra was watching,
and then she saw that I was giving him an ear or whatever,
and then she did,
and we kind of almost turned into something
where it's like,
She was sticking up for him. I was sticking up for him and then even and I next was sticking up for him and then
He was kind to us
at the beginning very self-spoken and and seemed like a victim almost and
slowly
insidiously, he began turning on us for really no reason and other people and
And going nuts. We're talking about are we talking about you brandy. Yeah, thank you. Yes, brandy cue and
You know we betrayed you guys
Go ahead betrayed you guys. No betrayed he just showed his true colors
And it's the same person that we see on those videos screaming and ranting and going nuts and talking to little girls
Yeah
And also all the people that are saying like, oh, you know, like a lot, a lot of people are against me anyway, so they're just looking for an opportunity to make me look stupid or make me look wrong or something like that.
But I'm here apologizing sincerely and, you know, saying I made a mistake.
And let me tell this because this is I think what happened with you. I try to support him everything and he got went crazy because Alex was helping him out and, you know, she was supporting him and she'd be in the chats.
his chats her and i were the only real people in the chat the others were bots
and so she supported him but he went nuts and turned on her because she was talking to his op he said
And then later, then, you know, with everything that we've all been through, people back and forth all the time, then, you know, I told him, hey, you know, talk to her, whatever.
And he had me, you know, suddenly, we're both against her because I didn't trust her anymore with whatever he was talking about, but he was lying, especially $1,000 donut and all that.
And I feel bad because I even shared that he was lying and he just turns on everybody and then I saw the true him, especially when he started texting me, I'm going to kill you.
um what was it uh go die and that's it recorded that's what yeah i'm showing all our texts
you know i did a video recording of our complete text and i have to put it in different parts
because they're long
And the recording's on text now.
I'm glad I recorded him going nuts and threatening me.
And he has a nerve to try to reach out again.
I won't ever take back some lunatic like that.
Exactly, exactly.
And I think the bad boy breeze must be a fake bad boy breeze
because he's the one hiding people.
And it's like, I just like, until we figure it out,
I'm just gonna-
Then yeah, then then, yeah, unmodern, that's Brandon.
Yeah, it must be Brandon.
That's Brandon.
Yeah.
I got a haircut chat you guys like my I was gonna say yeah, that looks great your hair cut because you look different
That's a nice haircut. Thank you. I went to a salon actually and got my hair cut
Do you know what a toncillary is?
What's the toncillary? I've never heard that it's like a barber shop. Okay. It's like a fancy fancy way of saying bar
It's like a gentrified barber shop
toncillary
Did you have a female female salon person?
I went to the salon because I had long hair, so they'd be better cutting it. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I got my hair cut by a female. Okay good
Yeah, it looks great. I like the haircut. It does but now the problem is now Joker now
He looked or mr. Extendo now now he looks even younger. I'm gonna get him even more. I know doesn't he like yeah, I'm 20 I'm 26
Okay, so let me see I'm gonna go in my mods real quick and just get the statement care of
Because friend. I mean a bad boy breeze. It's bad boy breeze 13. That's all he uses. Okay. I'm not sure if it was him
that did it, but we'll figure it out.
But I see bad boy breeze and then I see,
I think I see one bad boy breeze over this or two
that are modic because then he got on the other one.
Okay, I'm just gonna, I'll just have to do this one.
Okay, okay, let's take care of.
And if it's if I'm wrong, we'll figure it out later. Oh, he was hiding a lot of people. You said
Gamble, you know after that. So oh he hit gamble you mean? Yeah. Oh man
So yeah, bad boy breeze wouldn't hide gamble and
Yeah, I don't know this. Okay. Oh, I can know I can actually the clear out some of the mods too that you know
I have some managing mods. I know I can trust I said I can just make sure if I know everybody and
Yeah, because we're getting I try to put on subscriber only mode, but it's like it's very complicated to do and it's like
I wish it wasn't that hard to figure out, you know, yeah
I can direct you to do it psych if you need them to figure out do it. Yeah, I can tell you
All right, so look you go click on the you click on the go live button
And then you click on your open stream and then you go into you go into settings and then you scroll down
And it should be subscriber mode only. Okay
I'm studio or on the YouTube
on YouTube Studio.
Okay, okay, got it.
Okay, I think I got it.
Okay, live.
Are you on a computer, right?
I'm on a computer, yes.
Yeah, so it should be easier.
It's hard to do it on mobile.
So you just click go live and then you,
I'll walk myself through it.
Okay, I mean, I'm on the page where it's,
I'm just looking for subscribe only mode.
Comments, moderation, okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, what you see where it says you see where it has the title of your stream and it says edit next to it
Yeah, yeah, click that button edit and then just go to customization
Uh-huh, and then you'll be able to put it in sub mode only
Scroll down
Okay, I see it and then okay perfect. Okay, and then it says
Participants subscribers got it got it. And then one minute. I guess I just have bots coming in with
Doxy and so perfect. Okay. That was easy. Okay. Did it. Thank you so much
Subscriber only motive on thank you so much. Okay, perfect. That'll make chat better. Okay. Whoo
Okay
Yeah chat. So what's up vulgar? I see one of my viewers is here. What's up vulgar?
Yeah, I've been streaming call of duty the new call of duty on ps5 lately. That's what I've been doing
Yeah, so
No, it's like thank you for joining my stream the other night. I actually gained a lot of subs. Thank you
I didn't like that was so much fun. I love going on your stream and it was like it was just like
What are you still love about YouTube is just going to fun chats and just having fun and like like, you know
Talking shit in the mess around it was it was it was a lot of fun and mr.
It's like a it's like a call of duty lobby, you know
like everybody trash talking, yeah
Music he has his tts on like so every every every chatter, you know you need to hear your message
And it's like that. He's a pretty funny crazy chat
So it's mr. Extendo with a w is his channel and everyone make sure to subscribe and check it mr. Extendo, okay
E X T E N D O and then a W at the end to be honest like only only if you're in the call of duty and gaming if you're not
Yeah, gamers. Yeah, there's a lot of gamers. Oh too
But yeah, so was psych so today has been today been a chaotic day for you
It's been a good day. I mean, I woke up straight and it's like the first day someone had sent me
The INX had posted and I watched it and I saw the messages and I was pretty pretty shocking
I had no communication with him off of my show at all like at all. So I so it was just like purely
I
Don't have like, you know, he wasn't text messaging me or anything or you know
I'm sure I would have seen a lot of this sooner like and then he but I didn't notice like he would you know
you know putting me down and then he said oh he made the show and I would be nothing without him and
and then I mean all this kind of shit and I was like okay this is like ridiculous and so
yeah thank you I mean it's like you know I mean I tried to
Sort this out a few weeks ago, but I couldn't find the video and now that I had the video
I could finally play it and stuff like that
But I was I was even planning when he was still here to out to play it for him
So hey two hundred twenty-five viewers. Wow amazing. You get viewers and have you noticed that when he leaves it drops
Yeah, I mean, I mean when he gets on it it drops
Yeah, and he leaves a people come on and he was trying to say that he you get a lot of viewers when he's on that's bullshit
Yeah
I mean, so uh, I recently watched a video psych
I know this is kind of off topic
But I watched the video that the clumsy posted clumsy posted a clip of you are interviewing Brandon Q
And he was talking about he had a Russian or Maffordite girlfriend
Yeah, well, he's into Russians at Russians her Maffordites trans and femme boys. I guess that's just that's
Oh Brandon. Yeah
So does he like the bussy?
Yes, I guess so. I mean it's like but you know he likes and he's just like a
Kind of like it's just a weirdo. I don't know. He likes everything. He's like sick, right? Okay, so
Anyway, it's like we can like move on from this point. This means it's like I mean it would be great to like
You know, it's kind of like Baltimore. It's like just don't speak the name anymore and like, you know
Look, it's like this will be the even the end of any discussion of him or anything
He basically is a persona non grata or does not exist anymore to me
and so
To me everything is irrelevant. So as long as Brandon, he's like sticking weapons up his butt
Yeah, I guess he's like a gun of his butt or something like that. I'm not sure. Whoa. I didn't know that either
Damn, yeah, I mean, that's kind of
So chat I want to tell you guys so much at today I took a shower
Sike have you showered today?
No, I haven't I'm dirty right now, but if I was there
Hey, we have a guest. Let's see. Oh Lance Owens. Let me see Lance. Oh, and be careful. That's a
Someone's calling me on the phone. Okay. I'm gonna answer this. Okay. I'll join back though. I'll join back
Well, let's see this is yeah careful with you, you know, you got to be make a big screen of yourself
You know you just you so you can see who it is before you bring them on you got it. You got a device not connected lance
I'm sorry. I mean you have to connect your device or I can't have you on okay, so I'll take this down
It's him. I mean, it's crazy that he has all this time in the world of me making all these alts and
And all yeah, it's just you know, he doesn't have one single friend though. Either it's bad
Who's this I can't see your face Earl Dub
Yeah, that's him. It's him. It's he's playing games. Yeah
Can you play that video that I sent you just played that that's he's playing games
He's gonna he makes a hundred all to try to come in and screw with you. Oh my god
I'll play that video. He's backstage looking scary and like making faces at me
Because he's got mental issues. Yeah
Okay, we're surveyed so which video do you want to post it? I mean the one you played it earlier?
Yeah, the one that I sent you by text you can play it's from kick and that's what gumball was sending me
It was no virus. It's it's a video
I will send that again today and other videos too and I want to go ahead and use all the ones you have
Okay, I'm gonna go ahead and give my messages
Okay, and
So
Oh, maybe maybe a little late, but I guess seven. Hey guys, it's seven eleven
You know, I always knew this would be an important day the 7-eleven. Oh
Okay, so I do have the video ready this is from rumble brandy press the Mexican lady that her dog and destroys their crib
I mean, I say I really this is this is a trigger warning
I do not like to see any kind of like animal stuff done, but I mean it's like just in in the
of getting
I'm interested in the truth ultimately and it's like let's check it out yeah guys go to 711 today
you get a free slurpee any size I think sometimes it's when you brought in they brought in a uh
they bring in they brought in a uh big big barrel and they will fill the barrel with
okay okay let's see I'm gonna get it the rumble link okay I'm so sorry here we go got it okay put it
That's better than yours.
Okay, here we go.
There we go.
He presses the Mexican link.
Got it?
Okay, here we see.
This is why you should never trust your electric bills
after the COVID pandemic.
Jazz station, get some shit, bro.
Nigga!
You nigga!
I want you nigga to suck my dick, nigga!
I'm gonna end up having to stab this dog in the neck dude dude I'm gonna end up having
to stab this dog in the neck
dude what the fuck is wrong with you I'm not gonna end up having to kill a dog
over you no I'm not gonna have to kill a dog over here bro
bro let's just go let's just go no let's just go dude no let's just go let's just go
look it look it let's just go
just go ahead and call the police
Just go ahead and call the police, please
Just call them dude. No, no, no, no call them. Please call them
Brandon you're gonna get yourself arrested
You're gonna get yourself arrested stop, please
No, Brandon, please
please Brandon please stop please stop please stop Brandon please stop stop no
stop Brandon Brandon please stop okay go ahead
Come here, come here right now dog.
Right here, please.
What's up dog?
Yo dude, what's up dog?
What's up, come on, come on, come on.
Come on here, come here right here.
Come here right here, come on here.
Come on here, it's like a slide dog.
Come here, come here, it's like a slide dog.
Yeah, you scared bitch, you scared bitch.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know, right?
Damn, just crazy.
Yeah, I saw him, you know, I only got her property.
I already saw him trying to kill my dad.
This is terrible.
We have somebody backstage, but I don't know if they're real.
I just need to check up there real real quick,
because I'm, I don't know if they're real.
Yeah, it's him, he's crazy, no lie.
Okay, hold on a second, I'm up to the point.
Okay, Carolyn, Carolyn, are you a real person?
Can you wave to the camera?
Can you react to me in some way?
No, it's not a real person. It's just a fake
That's him again. Yeah, don't let him try to he's trying to interfere with you showing him on the video
Get the fuck over here. What the fuck are you doing? Stop doing that dude. You're invading
what the fuck are you doing what the fuck i'm sorry uh he's just he's just drunk um
here i'm trying to get him i'm not sure what he's doing and he's being crazy
Come come over here, please dude. Please come over here. No, you're invading someone's house
You're invading someone's house dude stop stop. This is not cool, and this is not content, bro
You're invading someone's house
You're invading someone's house you fucking retard what the fuck is wrong with you no no stop
stop stop doing this stop doing this stop doing this no you're you're
literally destroying so much property no just stop stop stop doing this dude
this is not cool at all this is not what you caught dude please please please
you are going to die
You are going to die dude. You are going to die stop
You're going to die you are going to die
Don't do niggas gazing niggas.
Invading someone's house.
Shot him and got away with it.
Neuropathy protocol Big Pharma doesn't want you to discover.
It'll end real quick.
Neuropathy is a completely reversible.
Come here.
are you doing bro you're fucking crazy oh no stop stop with what you're doing I
can't turn on my light and then get over here did you call the cops did you
call the police dude no stop did dude you're gonna get arrested dude what the
Maybe he has a death wish
You're stupid as fuck you're you're the most dumb ass retard and then there's fucking
There's fucking cops over at your house right now. You fucking retard
Did you call the car did you call the car?
Did you call the police did you call the police call the police
Call the police call the police
Dude, please stop doing this
Yo, you're gonna get arrested you're gonna get arrested you're gonna go to county jail for three days
Get the fuck over here
Here you're gonna go to county jail
We're not putting up this shit. You need to be a proper member of society
And you're literally fucking being a fucking psychotic piece of shit, and you're odd someone's property
get there you're you're you're you're literally making the dog worried and
you're making you're literally wearing the whole ass neighborhood bro no you're
literally wearing the whole ass neighborhood you piece of shit you're
a piece of shit scumbag and you're over here breaking someone's windows
You're breaking someone's windows you piece of shit get the fuck out of here
Get the fuck out of here now bro, we're not gonna deal with this shit get over here
Get the fuck up
get the fuck up and get out of their property get out of their property get
out of their property bro get out of their property get out of their
property right now stop saying things that are abusive you're gonna get
Hey, guess who, guess who, nigga, I'm gonna fuck you, man.
You're gonna get arrested, brother.
He wants to fuck the dog in here.
You're gonna get arrested.
You're gonna get arrested, brother.
get your ass up they're right here they're right here dude they're right
here they're right here right here you're gonna about to get arrested bro what
do you mean fuck me
There's no such thing! We're all equal!
We're all equal!
We're all equal, dude!
Dude, what the fuck?
You are fucking psychopathic, bro.
You're gonna get arrested.
You're getting arrested, bro.
You're getting arrested right now, dude.
Get the fuck
If it is, shut the fuck up, oh
Fuck howdy, oh, that was in the car
You said it's me, did you think you could do this video? No
I want you to do it
Yo, stop doing this shit
Stop doing this shit
Oh bro, this shit's gonna hurt bro
He's just insane because dogs never make you act like that.
This guy, he's going crazy right here.
This guy I've been recording in, he's on someone else's property and he's been kicking their door in and their car.
English speaker?
I'm not sure, you need to go talk to him.
Alright, so just go stand over there.
I'll stand right here on the sidewalk right here.
Hey, I'm looking for you. What's going on?
All right, I'm gonna stand right here on this corner all stand right here
And I'm not sure
I he just climbed over the fence I saw over the fence right here
It might be around this corner right here. Yeah, I'm gonna I'm just gonna stay right here
I think there's an opening on that end.
I'll help you.
Yes.
No.
Don't make it hurt anybody.
All right?
Just get over here.
Come over here.
We got food.
Send some food over here.
No.
It's not how it's going to work.
I'm going to need you to come over here, man.
I can get you some water. I can get you some stuff.
Man, you gotta come over.
Hey man, come on. Over the fence. Come on, man.
Just wait up here. No.
Where's gonna leave them?
No.
Man, I'm not playing around.
I'm easier to get on the other side of the fence now.
Over the fence.
Right here.
Come on, we're not in a minute. Let's go right now.
Come on, man.
You just need to arrest him. He's on someone else's property.
I just can't begin with you right now.
I'm just saying...
Open it! Open it right now!
Open it! Open it!
Come on, get over the fence!
No, stand the ground.
That's what I'm saying, me and you, let's get out.
Let's have a lot of raw sugar, you know what I'm saying?
Me and you act stupid, right?
Or do you want me to act stupid?
I want you to stop messing around. All right. Okay. Go sit over there, man. Yeah, I'm gonna stand here on the sidewalk
I just seen him he came over here and he started banging on this person's door
and call yeah I was walking down the street I was gonna go to the gas station
over there and then he just he started
oh no I just started recording I came up over here
yeah okay yeah yeah
I'm just gonna hang here
Can you stand up for us?
All right, ready?
One, two, three.
Let's go.
Okay.
One, two, three.
I said it was a lie.
I said when I see it, I didn't think it was a lie.
One, two, three.
You have to call me a pedophuser.
I'm just going to check to make sure you got a weapon.
Hold on, let me just check to make sure you got no weapons on you, alright?
I didn't do anything.
Brandon?
Okay.
That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying. If you want to go straight, you can take care of me.
You look a lot like everybody. What does that mean, Brandon?
That's what I'm saying.
What do you mean by go, I'm going to go crazy?
I just want to go live on this.
What's live? What does that mean?
Live on.
What does that mean?
You too.
Crazy.
Yeah bro, you were there with her, didn't you?
Yeah, I was about.
Alright, let me try.
Let me try.
What?
Oh yeah, I'll stand on the sidewalk over here.
Thank you very much.
See you in a minute.
Power companies are demanding the removal of a video posted
by a retired electrician.
The reason, thousands of viewers exposed to it
started paying less for electricity.
John Mayne spent 31 years.
I thought that was branded.
There's a cross that doesn't read.
I know.
Explaining what he calls dirty electricity.
I don't contain that in the book.
Uh-huh.
Brandon, how much have you had to drink today?
Here's liquor
Bro, what are you doing?
This is bad.
So, it was initially in the back row.
I put a jump rope in there.
Okay.
Just try to talk to him.
He ended up jumping over the fence.
He was already on the ground.
It was bad.
So, that's what you guys think.
Okay, that makes sense.
Sir, did you happen to see anything?
Because I was recording here.
Oh, yeah, I was walking with him,
and then he just jumped over the fence,
and then he recorded me.
Yeah, I know him.
Friends, blood related, acquaintance.
Acquaintance, kind of.
Okay, so obviously he's very intoxicated.
Yeah.
He what was he doing by jumping these people's fences? I'm not sure he lives right there
And then he just walked down the street, and then he wanted to harass the dog and then he started kicking in
Yeah, he started trying to take it. Yeah, I have been on recording here
Do you want to tell me what you saw
Um, I was just here and he just jumped over the fence and then he started harassing the dog and
banging on the car and then banging on the door and that that's pretty much it and then he started screaming
Did you see him trying to hit the dog at all or anything like that?
I mean he did go after the dog
Oh, no
I haven't given any information. Do you want me to provide anything?
No, I really wouldn't want to be involved.
But you kind of are because you're kind of standing around here with the phones.
Do you or do you not?
No, I don't want to be involved or anything.
Okay, for sure. You can head on out, man.
We don't need you anymore. We've got a good state for you.
Yeah, I'm just on the sidewalk and I'm just here.
Okay, I think it's just funny. Just contradicts that you don't want to be involved,
but you're kind of...
Well, I'm just here on the sidewalk. Yeah, I'm just walking.
This request is super disrespectful at that point, Radio 8.
Um, he doesn't know what to do, so I guess he jumped over the fence, and when he jumped over to him being alcohol-free, well,
the sense he kind of initiated the call.
He said it was drugs.
He said drugs.
Just in case.
Um, great.
Are you gonna start for him?
He acts like when he's sober, so you can't blame alcohol.
Okay.
How old do you know how old he is man 30s I wouldn't I wouldn't necessarily know
I could put him in a psychiatric ward for a while.
Which one was that?
That was, I think that was, uh, Griffin isn't here.
Go ahead and call Gonzalez.
I don't know. Go ahead and just tell me if he can send you 21 to call.
Since Griffin's not here, because I don't know whose voice that was.
Just have him 21 year on the phone and then just
It might just be a marijuana. I think he smoked marijuana and kind of
Mess with yeah, I kind of mess with this head. Yeah. Yeah, he smoked marijuana and you know, I was trying to I was trying to get him
Calm, but he just started freaking out and
I'm glad nobody was outside because I mean yeah
I mean, yeah, and we're just gonna walk to the gas station get some what I was gonna buy him some water and the Gatorade
He just got set off just and he just he just flipped out dude. He's saying
He did that to vegan too when an effort on video too
Are you coming with him?
Sorry for him
He went crazy
That's what he wanted to take
I know
Sorry about that
with him and like you guys were both trying to get in.
No.
No?
What happened?
I was walking to the gas station
to get a Gatorade with him to-
So you were with him?
Yes, we were walking and I was gonna go get some water.
And then-
Yeah, it's in the back.
I'll get it just in case.
And then when I was walking by here-
It's in my drawer.
All of a sudden-
all of a sudden he all of a sudden he jumped over all of a sudden he jumped
over this fence and I was like what are you doing it's weird I don't know him
know him he's just someone I ran into yeah yeah yeah yeah he yeah he was he
was yeah yeah
I was shocked. I was like, oh, no, what are you doing? I was trying to get him to
Yeah, I was like, oh my god. I was like, what are you doing? And then he started banging on your car
Yeah, he started banging on your car and and trying to break the windows and all that stuff. I was like really worried
Yeah
I was just like
I'll just like, man!
Look a beautiful dog look a friendly dog and he wanted to kill it
Hold on, just hold on.
He banged his head.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't, he's not here.
I remember starting telling us that.
I was just telling him, sorry,
you just let him know about it.
I don't, it's not a used to,
but if you want just to go over it with him.
Yeah.
I'll do your registry.
I'll just message you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just message him and just follow him.
Can't see what he has to say.
Yeah.
Because as long as we didn't have hands on him.
Okay.
Sorry about it. Everything like this. You know, he just he drank too much and
he started going crazy and then he started messing with the dog and all that. You know,
I was trying to get him to stop. Yeah, and he just he just started going crazy.
You know, it happens up here. It happens up here.
You know everyone gets and now he's hurting himself
Stop doing that. Yo, dude, stop doing that. That's not appropriate. No, no stop doing that
Should be gone. I hope it's not too hard for me.
Just let him know what's going on.
I'm gonna go look up this 49. He's not getting a sergeant, yes.
Just to see what's going on.
So, what if...
It all looks like this.
You don't have to jump in.
And then the place that shows up.
It's in the middle of the door.
And it's in the same dimension.
And later on...
Oh my God, he possibly exchanged this.
Yeah, no, no, I mean, this happened when you were here, so that's why I'm saying just to cover your butt, you know.
Okay, perfect.
And that sounds good.
It keeps the city safe.
He wanted to kill the dog as well.
He didn't even set it to him.
So perfect.
Damn.
They're going to take their dogs to the farm,
and there's like,
animal cruelty,
though they're going to die.
So I'm going to say to you.
So just farted one time,
and you just farted two.
Actually, can I go a little bit farther?
Actually, you might want to do more.
Yeah, since 39, they have a...
You have to give him the car?
Oh, we have to, like, drive in the back.
Yeah, we have to get it there. Yeah, definitely.
We can follow him, because I need...
Just because of my condition.
Yeah, because I don't want you to go by yourself.
And you want to go with Dylan, or if you want me to...
I could, yeah, I think I'd be able to be with Dylan,
but I do appreciate having someone with me.
So then, you'll handle it?
We'll have one of us follow you.
Alright, so we'll go with 43 though.
Did you just put for them? Did they, did he, did he actually put for them?
Okay, I'm gonna get so yeah, I'm gonna get back up in a second. Let me go my history. Okay. This is the this is the
Other stuff where he's just yeah, cuz I never saw it see I've seen all the other stuff
The only one I saw was the one the 13 year old girl that he was
flirting with and on monkey app
So and yeah, cuz I think it's maybe
You know we haven't seen it
Everybody needs to see it. They've been out. You know, I just didn't see all of those and and they try to send it to me
It didn't open right here. We go. Okay. Enjoy. Well
And he's gonna try to come up with fake accounts. Don't let them especially when you're showing him. Just let it play
Yep, I want gamble to get married bro and have a daughter
Good girl. It wouldn't she told me that
I want you to row
He's the best with him
Then you'll see what a PDF is bro. I'll show you then I'll show you PDF
That's the one I saw I
Promise you I'm not an alcoholic
I'm gonna be honest. I'm not even in high school yet. I drink like this. I'm going into high school
When I'm in high school more than me, I would already be old fucker. What a weirdo. She's a kid 13
But I'm in high eighth grade. Trust me. I was bringing shit to school. No, I hate when people call me an alcoholic
He's killing her, check this out.
Prove it, prove it.
Prove it.
That's why he was harassing me.
That's child, that's a child, that's a child, that's a child, that's a child, that's a child.
She's 15.
Exactly, bro.
And this dude, Michelle, Ashley, is a minor.
I don't even know who Ashley is, bro.
That's a fake profile, bro.
Go ahead and ban Ashley.
Where's Ashley in the chat, bro?
All right, Ashley, you're banned, bro.
I'm glad my vibe is childish, bro.
I hope you do.
Hello.
Who are you?
Yeah.
Why are you talking shit on stream?
Oh, so you're actually, is this Ashley?
Is this Ashley?
Who are you then?
What the hell?
Presented.
Whatever.
No, I'm not recording you, bro.
I'm not recording you.
I didn't record you, bro.
That's just your casual day today, and I got a girlfriend, bro
Bro, you live with your fucking daddy bro in your fucking dad's house, bro
This dude's girlfriend. This dude's girlfriend doesn't even fucking live nowhere near him, bro
The pussy's calling me dude. Hey, what's up pussy?
Hey, what's up, bitch? Shut the fuck up
Shut the fuck up watch what I'm in Florida. You fucking pussy fuck funny thing, bro
A chick literally said that a chick a chick lied about getting raked with him, bro. Hello
Hey, what's up coward you didn't do shit shut your fucking mouth, bro
What's going on coward what are you sure yeah, what okay, so what's gonna happen now?
I'm gonna beat you dad this time dude
And I'm gonna fucking leave you
You're fucking delusional
What you just did
You're fucking
Congrats
Kill yourself bro
Kill yourself
Don't
Look at who's the one bro
Who are the people that got me almost put in prison bro
For the rest of my life and caused me this pain bro
Fuck
Yeah
Fuck you
Fuck yeah
FUCK YOU! I'll be motherfuckers BAM, BRUH!
I'll be drop a nuclear bomb on all you motherfuckers, BRUH!
FUCKING DIE, BITCH!
I'll be motherfuckers DIE!
It's oh, I great. Oh, I great you. Oh, he great me dude. And then she's saying oh, I said I didn't say you great me
I said that you she said this I have her on recording saying this she said that I didn't say you great me
I said that you come inside me unconcentrally
Haha, you're a fucking idiot dude. That's what she said. She tried saying that she said that I that I come dinner
Unconsensually, bro. Fuck you pussy. You know you're yeah
Fuck pussy
Fuck you, bro
Fuck your bitch ass, bro. You're a pussy, dude. Fuck you. I'm so fucked in the head, dude
I've already so you are almost happened to me bro where I've almost been sent to prison for the rest of my life
Bro for shit. I didn't do dude
I felt that way bro, or I felt I felt in a way bro where we're trying to do that
Drunk again
Fuck you motherfuckers that do that shit, bro that have tried to set me up, bro
Try to fucking get me in trouble, dude or try to from everything bro. I'm not even talking about just this dude
I'm talking about everything bro all the people that have tried to lie on me or try to set me up, dude
Get me killed get me fired bro make me be homeless bro all that shit
something motherfucker I want you to do something bitch it's gonna get worse it's
always gonna get worse do something pussy he's crying I want you what
coward it's gonna get worse it's gonna get worse shut up pussy you ain't gonna
do shit do something fucker do something bitch do something
You son of a fucker!
My memory, I can't even remember what the fuck it was.
It's cause it was alcohol, alcoholic, bro.
You don't remember that?
No, but when I rape you.
Brandon's gonna be out here in 10 minutes.
This is fucking...
You know what, bro?
I hope somebody really does fucking rape you, bitch,
and fucking kills you, bitch!
Fuck you!
I hope that bitch really does get raped, bro.
I hope somebody fucking rapes her
and shoots her in the back of the fucking head, bitch.
Rapes her in the fucking ass, and boom, bro.
Blast her in the back of the motherfucking head, bitch.
Fuck you, cock!
Dumb bitch!
You fucking dumb bitch!
Fuck you!
They're trying to make me have a mental breakdown, bro.
You're on mental case.
You bitch!
Fuck you!
Why you don't do shit bitch except sit on your fucking ass, bro, and take pills like a fucking junkie bitch
Fuck you, bro
Well, it's obviously bullshit. So shut the fuck up. Post it pussy post it
post it post it
Post it coward
Shut up pussy. You're a bitch dude. Shut the fuck up, bro. Shut
Fuck you, bro
Shut up. You're a bitch. Fuck you, dude
Fucking pussy ass bitch. Yeah, I'm a fucking pussy, dude
I'm gonna fuck her soft as fuck, dude. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck
Shut your fucking mouth, bro
Shut the fuck up
He told the cops that I raped her dude
You did
I don't know, guns, it stays in me
But you put a gun to my head when you said that shit
Oh my god
You don't remember that?
I don't know when I rape you
YOU MOTHERFUCKER
I don't give a fuck, I just bossed myself
How about that bro?
I'm gonna beat you guys this time dude
And I'm gonna fucking rape you
AHHHHH
FUCKING DIE
Okay, did you know, contact me
Contact me, what about a lawyer?
Hey pussy, you're gonna get cancer and AIDS and DIE PUSSY!
Fuck yeah!
This fucking nasty ass shit away, bro.
Ugh, bro, I'm gonna throw the fuck up, bro.
Ugh, bro.
Ugh, dude.
Fuck is this, dude.
Who the fuck this is, bro?
Ugh, ugh, ugh.
Ugh, dude.
Ugh, bro.
I need to just don't hold the scene, there's no fucking cat, dude.
He's throwing the whole fucking box in that motherfucker, dude.
Ain't no fucking cat over here, bro.
Fuck, dude.
Ugh!
Fuck that.
Hey, pussy, dude, stop fucking calling me bitch!
You live with your fucking dad, bro.
You're a fucking bitch, bro.
Fuck you!
William Witt, bro.
You live with your fucking daddy, bro,
in your fucking dad's house, bro.
This dude's girlfriend doesn't even fucking live
nowhere near him, bro.
Who the fuck is the pussy's calling me, dude?
Hey, what's up pussy?
Hey, what's up bitch? Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up!
Watch what I'm in for, you fucking pussy!
Fuck you!
Fucking pussy.
He's a fucking bitch!
Dude, bitch you ass mother fucker!
Call back bitch!
Hey, what's up you fucking fanboy?
Hey fanboy!
Hey fanboy, hey fanboy, shut the fuck up you fucking pedophile shut your pedophile ass up motherfucker
You're a fucking pedophile, bro. You're a fucking pedophile shut the fuck up
Shut the fuck up. You're a fucking pedophile bitch. You fucking rape kids. Fuck you
Pedophile motherfucker you fucking bag it
Fuck you, bro. I don't give a fuck, dude. Fuck you, bro.
I'm gonna go talk to my 15-year-old girlfriend, guys. Gonna hurry, everybody.
He's sick, man. All those kids, you know.
Snowballs.
He was right about him the whole time.
Literally gonna go talk to my 15-year-old girlfriend guys good night guys the one he put a gun to her head
He's insane man, he should be put away
I'm gonna go talk to my 15-year-old girlfriend, bro my 12-year-old girlfriend is victim
Well, you know sounds like he's like mentally. He's mentally ill. It's it's yeah, it's it's mental in that little girl
This is the other
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come
I have no idea he was this sick you're going to die you are going to die
How old are you? 15. Oh my god, dude. She looks like she's 15. They're beautiful.
You have a boyfriend or what? Yeah, you do?
Bro that 15 year old was cute.
She looks like fun. Stand around.
That's what I'm saying. Me and you, let's stand up.
Me and you act stupid, right? Or do you want me to act stupid?
I want you to stop messing around, all right?
Okay.
Go sit over there, man.
He's English.
He's English?
Okay.
Who's this guy over here?
Uh, I just seen him, uh, he came over here and he started banging on this person's, uh, door.
I'm just gonna check and make sure you got weapons.
Hey, bro, what are you doing here?
Hold on, let me just check and make sure you got no weapons on you, all right?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Brandon?
Yeah.
Okay.
How much have you had to drink today?
10 drinks, beers, liquor. What are we talking about? Liquor? What type of liquor?
Okay, I can't tell. But what type? Whiskey? Tequila?
Okay, so we're gonna set you in here, okay? All right, go ahead and step inside.
Watch your step, watch your step.
Stop doing that yo dude stop doing that that's not appropriate
I'm gonna drink this and then I'm gonna have the whole stream bro
I'm gonna drink this and then I'm ending the whole fucking stream, bro. Fuck this shit, bro
Let him tuck tail and turn and run. Hey gamble. Hey did the ex bro. I fuck I own you bro
How does it feel that I own you bro? Like I said, bro
go have a baby bro like I said bro go have a baby bro your girlfriend her
uterus is cursed go have a baby bro go do it go get married go get married bro
I was on his nuts or whatever he played me like a fiddle played me like a fiddle
I was talking about how my dad used to build saltwater aquariums bro this dude
goes all out studying and researching bro so he could build his own saltwater
aquarium bro clown bro you're a clown bro
You're a clown bro, and now you're gonna go through all this because of Anita bro
I was gonna leave you alone bro despite you threatening my mom bro. I was gonna let let it slide bro
I'm telling you, bro. I was gonna let everything slide bro. I'm about to end this bro. Good night guys
I see it's one of those nights that
I'm outie bro. I'm out of here, bro. I'm out of here guys. Good night Q army. Good night
Everybody I need to go talk to somebody dude. All right guys. Good night later everybody
Ooh, what am I looking for?
I got this one, sir.
Is this one, sir?
Can we share some?
Can we share, like, uh...
Oh, sure.
I told you, bro.
Get you a beer.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Where are we going again?
I have to go to the gym now.
I'm on my- whatever you're on bro
What am I on?
I'm a zombie
cause I asked him how much it's gonna cost
Don't come to a restaurant and act like that bro
That's how you can act
I'm always gonna-
Yeah you're totally right, yeah
I'm gonna call my dad and chase him
I'm on my- whatever you're on bro
What am I on?
I'm a zombie
I'm just an only broken people are trying to work dude
you're like a howling annoying person bro like people don't care dude
all the shit you say you want to ask and shit fuck bro
uh okay
i wanted to be on the streamer
oh i saw the fuck head in
shut the fuck up you're an idiot
i want to i want to spread the hate
i'm gonna hate you bro
yeah you need to do it
nigger sit down nigger sit the fuck down
wait wait what the fuck are you doing to me
sit down
Get down and we're gonna choke you and we're gonna make the bulldozer
Brandon, please please Brandon
Please what please stop? Don't abuse me. Don't abuse me. Don't abuse me, dude
What the fuck are you talking?
What the fuck you don't know I don't want your cock bro. I don't fuck you you talking about
Don't let's go
Let's go get water
Get your phone
Get your phone right now and let's go get some drinks and then he goes
We need some Gatorade's and we need some stuff to make sure that you're okay, bro
No, it's not about ah, yeah
It's not about ah
We're supposed to be fucking homies, dude. We're supposed to pick each other up whenever we when whenever the
Message calls us. No, it's not about that
You're not supposed to be doing all these drugs you're not supposed to be doing all these drugs
And you're not supposed to be doing all this shit, bro
My mom learned it, she saw it, said whatever I do with mom, look!
She's scary, I do it.
We got rid of him when he was a kid.
I want to suck on a 17 year old pussy dude.
Straight boner dude.
Straight fucker.
Put 17 year old pussy.
I want Gamble to get married bro and have a daughter dude.
I want you to bro.
Then you'll see what a PDF is bro.
I'll show you then, I'll show you PDF.
I'm going to go talk to my 12 year old girlfriend right now.
Oh, my God.
Is my asshole pretty spread open or what?
Oh, no!
You want to fuck me in the ass or what, Gamble?
Wow.
So he wants gamble. He's so obsessed with gamble
And he's like bad boy breeze was in the chat. He goes well, he's gay. He's gay
But there he's wanting to you know hump a guy that guy that he said was gambles friend
Yeah, I mean he was I don't want anything to do with them now that I have my eyes open everything because I only saw that one video before and I actually thought
Okay, well
What a predator do you want to go have a baby bro like I said bro go have a baby
Okay
That's a mind-blowing. I had no idea good Lord
But they're more there's more videos or that's yeah, that was that was that was I mean I that was all I had but see even
Yeah, you didn't see like the bill like sometimes when you see videos
It's like you don't know the context of them, but it's like I think we've seen enough to get the content
Yeah, yeah, exactly. That's enough. But yeah, I want to use those too. I mean that it's crazy
I didn't really realize he was that insane
How can these girls little kids and talking about gaping guys and he's insane
How many news of Brandon, I don't know, there's him.
I guess he was, I guess Gamble asked one night,
asked him to show his butt hole and he spread it open
or something, but.
Yeah, no, right.
And then he's over there calling you and bad boy,
Breeze Gay, he's gay, gay, but apparently he is.
And he's obsessed with Gamble because Gamble isn't gay.
So that's probably why that, you know, he,
I mean, Gamble's always in his mouth.
I mean, Gamble, Gamble, Gamble.
But damn, yeah, I hope you I'm gonna go ahead. Oh, can I share your live?
Absolutely, I'll do that then I'll do that and
I'll make a video of it and I'll just put your name on top or whatever, you know
That's open to every for everybody to see because a lot of times when you share to your post not everybody's able to see it
I think I don't know. Yeah, thank you. I'll be good. Oh, okay. I'll do that. Yeah. Thank you psyche
So yeah, this is great great live. We're people that like had open minds about things and you know
We're willing to give the benefit of the doubt and it's like it just really fit us and so
I just hope that this is like, you know, anybody that had the question about it. I know right and now people shouldn't have a question
I had no idea, you know, now I realize he's sick and that's we're dealing with a crazy person that doesn't stop and
Everything with him is recorded and including the calls and I've already made a report on him
And he's still trying to call me right before you're live
Even like just friendly like talking making friends and like being friendly with some people like, you know
and then, but he finds, he sees that and he, he was jealous.
He can't stand it. Yeah. You saw the text where he's accusing me of knowing or being friends with
somebody named Tyler that goes by BSR. I don't know those people.
Yeah. Tyler is ghost. Tyler is ghost. Yeah. Yeah. Tyler is ghost. Now who's BSR? He said BSR is Tyler.
So I guess he saw me talking to ghosts. Me and ghosts are cool. Yeah. We talk outside.
outside of there. Yeah, very like a possessive obsessive. Yeah
He's so controlling that he doesn't want other people he talks to to talk to anybody else ain't those crazy
We saying you were
We mean there were signs that he was
Like we saw some some signs
No, it wasn't all there and we maybe didn't take him as seriously as we should and so but just I just want people to know
No, no, and and I hope you and Alex you guys were best friends and I don't know what happened
But I know like with me and her it started with him
We were supporting him and look how everything went to hell him too and it's like you know, it's like really like you know
if she's gonna do some investigating, maybe, you know, go further into, I mean, she's been into New Mexico and everything, but she's been not, you know what, maybe that's what she needs to do, maybe that's why she's there, she's not there to get him to impregnate her, she didn't call him or get with him, so she's there for a reason, so he's dangerous.
Stuff like that, he's very insecure and jealous, and it's like, that's probably the reason, he didn't come here trying to like, you know, clear his name or anything, he came here to start trouble.
accounts and I mean he's insane yeah and so so he will uh he'll be a bq
free stream you know he'll be the he's called Burger Queen from now on the
bq yeah right and I guess he's talking me on your lives and stuff because he was
questioning Tyler and said Tyler is BSR I said I don't know BSR
Well, that's you go ghost will take care of him. Oh, yeah, he will he's a great guy. I'll talk to him offline
He's a great guy, and I like talking to him. Yeah, he's a night owl mostly, you know
And yeah, he's up and when I'm sleeping so but we've had some good combos
And he's really a good guy and a good friend to you
I'll tell him about him. Yeah, he does go at people. I've noticed that before before I got to know him. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Tyler our ghost is a
He's like he has like a kind of abrasive like his his personality on on streams
But then like, you know, I've talked to him privately too and he's just like a sweetheart a person
Yeah, I like him. Yeah, cuz he I thought he was seemed like a bully online and people are scared of him
So yeah, you said he'll go after Brandon good cuz I'll talk to him about him and tell him how he brought him up
Cuz I didn't know what who B.s.r. Is like
He has a problem with me talking to other people and saying,
you're probably friends with Crisco again.
No, we're not.
I said, I was just trying to get the video and she didn't send it to me.
So I thought maybe it was a lie.
That's it.
But I don't even know the guy.
It doesn't matter who I talked to or Tyler or whoever.
It's none of his business and he goes nuts.
Yeah, but great live psyche and I'll go ahead and share your I love you too
So I'm gonna show it stop raining again. God. I hate this bipolar weather. So we'll talk later. Okay?
Okay, you have a great day. Okay, you too. Bye. Bye
okay guys like
My wrap this one up, but um, yeah, you know, we all learn lessons in life and there's some
Very great lessons, but you know hard lessons right, but yeah
So that's that's so that's where we were right? That's where we were
I'll be right back. Hmm. I
Love you guys. Thank you. Oh, yeah, but it did turn into like those. Oh, let's go attack psyche and they could have like people
could have done expose days on him like instead of like going after me and stuff like, you know
what's me now I'm a criminal gang leader because I'm like I'm gonna attack juggalos and
And, you know, because they say I stole like a $2 cigar from a story I go to every day on tape and everything when I didn't.
And that's going to be the extent of my criminal history right of it, right?
Okay, get back.
Candles bend in sideways, serpents in the sky
Every whispered secret comes back here to die
I saw the moon split open like a wound across the night
Silver angels hanging backwards with their halos burning white
Cathedral's made of televisions chanting through the fog
Every face distorted underneath the voice of God
Something waits for the other side
Little first trip, I was in the garden just having a laugh
Till I'm across my path
Hey you guys, do you want some more Trilla?
I could get you a little one of two ways
What's it gonna fit me?
I said I felt like the whole world was taking me
To re-fire the fire before my enemies
Till the little ones stop on me
Say it, I forgot the whole world begging me
To mean fire the love upon my enemies
Now I'm washed over me, washed over me as a retain
Yeah, be secure, I'll be gone as a retain
Be secure, I'll be gone as a retain
There's a way to be secure, retain
We can through the ceiling cracks black handles melting onto tarot stacks television angels
whisper through the snow every channel says there's nowhere left to go underneath the floor
Sick above her mosa waves
Like God Abandoned California to graves
Everybody online smiling with dead
I post in pretty lips while the real world
Retrieve gets louder every mirror grows teeth
Every whisper secret underneath my sheets
I can feel the static breathing in the wall
Hear invisible things crawling through the cause
What?
Welcome to Psyche's Nightmare
The ocean turned the every wave with smiling strangers
They're too long a while
Chase you some nightmare study prophecies that refuse to die
But the nightmare made me powerful to bring to something
Comes a ritual flame every camera lens becomes a summoning frame
Kristen's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Braun's chicken struts around but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea's gone sour Bita's bitter Betty again
Alexander had my back, that's a real one, not pretend
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the jealous gather up, begging for attention
Thirsty and stuck, one club I'm happy I'm not part of
Go hate yourself, hate yourselves
Bronze chicken, pluck those feathers, toss it in the pan, make it fried.
All that noise you're making can't hide the hurt inside.
Aim for a spotlight, but the stage is all mine.
Every hater's just a chorus that proves I'm doing it.
Welcome to the Psychi Hater's Club
Where the jealous gather up begging for attention
Thirsty and stuck, one club I'm happy I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Hate yourselves
Hell, lack of rerun show
Taking all their drama
But it's all for show
I'll keep rising
watch me shine
haters club stays left behind
come to the psyche
haters club
where the jealous gather up
the tension thirsty and stuck
one club i'm happy i'm not part of
go hit
i'm alone
i'm alone now
fantasies place my skull
like alkalites in a corridor
i keep seeing you as the perfect kind
Not because you were real, but because my hunger can paint halos on emptiness
I almost had you, or I almost had the idea of you
But it was in time, so let's follow the lessons we never got to learn
And I practiced not thinking about how easily I would've loved you
If the universe had opened the door an inch wider
I miss you, and I never met you, I miss you
And I never met you, I'm a loner, I'm a loner
And it's okay to cry, they said I was selfish
But all I did was carry you like a secret scripture
Tell me are they selfish, when I'm the one boss
Sometimes I inter-self, sometimes the blood in my head
Turns into sermons, if I'm such a creator
Why can't I make you, why can't I conjure you
Out of breath and need and she abusing
I miss you
And I'll never let you
I'll never let you
I'm alone, I'm alone, I'm alone
And in my place where my prayers go answered
I'll sing you the very night in the temple
I set the altar with bad intentions and good time
And in this pit just to graduate to Hexen
It's perplexing how they stay alive while staying infected
Bring energy to unbug the cerebral
no discomfort ever grows from rewarding exactly what they've earned
I'm done pretending I'm a bull not until every angel finally falls asleep
and the demons start whispering and start speaking in caption
this is real life and your kind sleep walks in fear it's a personality
what can they do that they haven't done for years
You sell your sins like souvenirs, limited drops on topology, premium tip
Profit from another's tears, Lincoln bio, got his good shipiness here
Preach the light then twist the dark ring like halo, hands full of knives
You built your church from stolen hearts and particles
You need a misconception, sure
Point is, it's ain't straight in your direction
You think you're safe behind your lens, your little privacy, your shadow
Ways of me like an old
I'm done floating above
Take the trigger in
Demons don't lie, they just get promoted
This is real life
And your kind's gonna extinct
Not from death, from backbone
They haven't for you
Tricks and pending doom
Yeah, mixing weed and how you want control back
A hex to you
You spot might be for you